var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "آزَرَ",
        "answer": "Azar",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "āzara",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(to) Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Ibrahim ",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِبِلِ",
        "answer": "the camels",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ibili",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَائِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their fathers",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ābāihim",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your forefathers",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ābāukum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاؤُنَا",
        "answer": "our forefathers",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ābāunā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَبِيهِ",
        "answer": "to his father",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "li-abīhi",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "tatīhim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "will come to them",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yatīhim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "atāhum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَأْتِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "so that you bring to them",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "fatatiyahum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "(there) came to you",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "atākum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَتْكُمُ",
        "answer": "(there) came to you",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "atatkumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "to bring [back] to you",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yatīkum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "comes to you",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "atākum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "ائْتِنَا",
        "answer": " Come to us. ",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "i'tinā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "come to you",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yatikum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِيَهُمُ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "tatiyahumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yatiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yatiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِي",
        "answer": "(when) comes",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yatī",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "We have given them",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "they were given",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "We gave it",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "We gave them",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "We gave them",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "we are given",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "nu'tā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "was given",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتُوا",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "waātū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "He has given you",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "tlit": "ātākum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآتٍ",
        "answer": "(is) sure to come",
        "pcklId": "535",
        "tlit": "laātin",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِثْمِ",
        "answer": "[the] sins",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-ith'mi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِثْمَ",
        "answer": "[the] sin",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-ith'ma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرًا",
        "answer": "any reward",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ajran",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَّلْتَ",
        "answer": "You appointed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ajjalta",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلًا",
        "answer": "a term ",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ajalan",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَجَلٌ",
        "answer": "and a term",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wa-ajalun",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلٌ",
        "answer": "(the) term",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ajalun",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلَنَا",
        "answer": "our term",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ajalanā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدَكُمُ",
        "answer": "(to) anyone of you",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "aḥadakumu",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "then We seized them",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhnāhum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We seized them",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "akhadhnāhum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذَ",
        "answer": "took away",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "akhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْخَذْ",
        "answer": "will it be taken",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yu'khadh",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَّخِذُ",
        "answer": "I (should) take",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "attakhidhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَتَّخِذُ",
        "answer": "Do you take",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "atattakhidhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "bil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "bil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "bil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةُ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiratu",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) another",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرِينَ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "ākharīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرِينَ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "ākharīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِخْوَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their brothers ",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'wānihim",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "[when]",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذِ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "idhi",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and then",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their ears",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "ādhānihim",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُوذُوا",
        "answer": "and they were harmed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waūdhū",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "(of) the earth",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "(of) the earth",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْحَاقَ",
        "answer": "Isaac",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "is'ḥāqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْمَاعِيلَ",
        "answer": "And Ishmael",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-is'māʿīla",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْفَكُونَ",
        "answer": "are you deluded",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tu'fakūna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَلَ",
        "answer": "it set",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "afala",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَلَ",
        "answer": "it set",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "afala",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَلَتْ",
        "answer": "it set",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "afalat",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآفِلِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones that set",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-āfilīna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكُلُوا",
        "answer": "So eat",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "fakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْكُلُوا",
        "answer": "you eat",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "takulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْكُلُوا",
        "answer": "eat",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "takulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُكُلُهُ",
        "answer": "(are) its taste",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "ukuluhu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "616",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "unless",
        "pcklId": "617",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "618",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "619",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "unless",
        "pcklId": "620",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "621",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "622",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "623",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "624",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "625",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "626",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "627",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "628",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "629",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "324",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those (to) whom",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those whom",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "332",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "333",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "334",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "what",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "[those] who",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those whom",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "347",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) ones who",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالَّذِي",
        "answer": "Like the one",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "ka-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "Who",
        "pcklId": "351",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِي",
        "answer": "to the One Who",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "lilladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) ones whom",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) ones whom",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those whom",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those whom",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those (to) whom",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "371",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "373",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "374",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "376",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "377",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّتِي",
        "answer": "with that",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "bi-allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةً",
        "answer": "(there are) gods",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ālihatan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٌ",
        "answer": "(is) God",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ilāhun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٌ",
        "answer": "(is the) god",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ilāhun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةً",
        "answer": "(as) gods",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ālihatan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(be) to Allah",
        "pcklId": "1016",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1017",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "To Allah",
        "pcklId": "1018",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1019",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1020",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1021",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1022",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1023",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "By Allah",
        "pcklId": "1024",
        "tlit": "wal-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(with) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1025",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1026",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1027",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1028",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1029",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1030",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah ",
        "pcklId": "1031",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1032",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(than) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1033",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(be) to Allah",
        "pcklId": "1034",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1035",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1036",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1037",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1038",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1039",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1040",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1041",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "for Allah",
        "pcklId": "1042",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "1043",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1044",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1045",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1046",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1047",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1048",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1049",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1050",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "with Allah",
        "pcklId": "1051",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1052",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1053",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1054",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1055",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah (revealed it)",
        "pcklId": "1056",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1057",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1058",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1059",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1060",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1061",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "with Allah",
        "pcklId": "1062",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1063",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1064",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1065",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1066",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "by Allah",
        "pcklId": "1067",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1068",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1069",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1070",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1071",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1072",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1073",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1074",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1075",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1076",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1077",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1078",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1079",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1080",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "to Allah",
        "pcklId": "1081",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(is) for Allah",
        "pcklId": "1082",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1083",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "for Allah",
        "pcklId": "1084",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1085",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1086",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah ",
        "pcklId": "1087",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1088",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1089",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1090",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1091",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1092",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1093",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1094",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "With Allah",
        "pcklId": "1095",
        "tlit": "falillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1096",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1097",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1098",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1099",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1100",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(are) for Allah",
        "pcklId": "1101",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1102",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "on",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "to me",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "upon Him",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "to me",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "to me",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمُ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "ilayhimu",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to it",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمُ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "ilaykumu",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to it",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "[to]",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "[to]",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "to me",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلْيَاسَ",
        "answer": "and Elijah ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-il'yāsa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَسَعَ",
        "answer": "and Elisha",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-yasaʿa",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ami",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَّا",
        "answer": "or what",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ammā",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ami",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَّا",
        "answer": "or what",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ammā",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِرْتُ",
        "answer": "[I] am commanded",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "umir'tu",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُمِرْنَا",
        "answer": "and we have been commanded",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wa-umir'nā",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِرْتُ",
        "answer": "I have been commanded",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "umir'tu",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْرُ",
        "answer": "the matter",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "l-amru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْرُ",
        "answer": "the matter",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "l-amru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their affair",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "amruhum",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّ",
        "answer": "(the) mother",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "umma",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) communities",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "umamun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَمٍ",
        "answer": "nations",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "umamin",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٍ",
        "answer": "community",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "ummatin",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "will they believe",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "yu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) believe",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيُؤْمِنُنَّ",
        "answer": "they would surely believe",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "layu'minunna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they will believe",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "yu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "to believe",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "liyu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْمِنَ",
        "answer": "we will believe",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "nu'mina",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَتْ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "āmanat",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْأَمْنِ",
        "answer": "to security",
        "pcklId": "566",
        "tlit": "bil-amni",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْنُ",
        "answer": "(is) the security",
        "pcklId": "567",
        "tlit": "l-amnu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their belief",
        "pcklId": "618",
        "tlit": "īmānahum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانُهَا",
        "answer": "its faith",
        "pcklId": "619",
        "tlit": "īmānuhā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانِهَا",
        "answer": "its faith",
        "pcklId": "620",
        "tlit": "īmānihā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "699",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "700",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُنْثَيَيْنِ",
        "answer": "the two females",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-unthayayni",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُنْثَيَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(of) the two females",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-unthayayni",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُنْثَيَيْنِ",
        "answer": "the two females",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-unthayayni",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُنْثَيَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(of) the two females",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-unthayayni",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسِ",
        "answer": "(from) the mankind",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-insi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسِ",
        "answer": "the mankind",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-insi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسِ",
        "answer": "the men",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-insi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْإِنْسِ",
        "answer": "and [the] men",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wal-insi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "so how",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fa-annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "How",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلُهَا",
        "answer": "while their people",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "wa-ahluhā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the former (people)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلُ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "awwalu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٍ",
        "answer": "any sign",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "āyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Signs",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "biāyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٍ",
        "answer": "sign",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "āyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Verses",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a Sign",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "biāyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٌ",
        "answer": "a Sign",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "āyatun",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "a Sign",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "[in] Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "in Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Verses",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Verses",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(are) signs",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "laāyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٌ",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "āyatun",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتُ",
        "answer": "the signs",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "l-āyātu",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "in His Verses ",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "biāyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٌ",
        "answer": "a Sign",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "āyatun",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Verses",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِي",
        "answer": "My Verses",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "āyātī",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "[with] (the) Verses",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسُنَا",
        "answer": "Our punishment",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "basunā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسَ",
        "answer": "violence",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "basa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسُهُ",
        "answer": "His wrath",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "basuhu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسَنَا",
        "answer": "Our wrath",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "basanā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَأْسَاءِ",
        "answer": "with adversity",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "bil-basāi",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "and in the sea",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "and the sea",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wal-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "and the sea",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wal-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدِيعُ",
        "answer": "Originator",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "badīʿu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبَدِّلَ",
        "answer": "one (can) alter",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "mubaddila",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبَدِّلَ",
        "answer": "one can change",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "mubaddila",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدَا",
        "answer": "became manifest",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "badā",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْدُونَهَا",
        "answer": "you disclose (some of) it",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tub'dūnahā",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرِيءٌ",
        "answer": "free",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "barīon",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرِيءٌ",
        "answer": "free",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "barīon",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَرِّ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-bari",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَرِّ",
        "answer": "(of) the land",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-bari",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَرِّ",
        "answer": "(of) the land",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-bari",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبَارَكٌ",
        "answer": "blessed",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "mubārakun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبَارَكٌ",
        "answer": "blessed",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "mubārakun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَازِغًا",
        "answer": "rising",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bāzighan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَازِغَةً",
        "answer": "rising",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bāzighatan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَاسِطُو",
        "answer": "(are) stretching out",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "bāsiṭū",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْسَلَ",
        "answer": "is given up to destruction",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tub'sala",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُبْسِلُوا",
        "answer": "are given to destruction",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ub'silū",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشَرٍ",
        "answer": "a human being",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "basharin",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبَشِّرِينَ",
        "answer": "(as) bearer of glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "mubashirīna",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْصَرَ",
        "answer": "sees",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "abṣara",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْصَارَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your sight",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "wa-abṣārakum",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَبْصَارُ",
        "answer": "the visions",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-abṣāru",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَبْصَارَ",
        "answer": "(all) the vision",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-abṣāra",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْصَارَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their sights",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "wa-abṣārahum",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "and the seeing one",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "wal-baṣīru",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصَائِرُ",
        "answer": "enlightenment",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "baṣāiru",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَطَنَ",
        "answer": "(is) concealed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baṭana",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُطُونِ",
        "answer": "(the) wombs",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "buṭūni",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَاطِنَهُ",
        "answer": "and the secret",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wabāṭinahu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْعَثُهُمُ",
        "answer": "will resurrect them",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yabʿathuhumu",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْعَثُكُمْ",
        "answer": "He raises you up",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yabʿathukum",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْعَثَ",
        "answer": "send",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yabʿatha",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَبْعُوثِينَ",
        "answer": "(will be) resurrected",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "bimabʿūthīna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "baʿdihim",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِ",
        "answer": "after it",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "baʿdihi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِكُمْ",
        "answer": "after you",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "baʿdikum",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "baʿḍahum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "with others",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "bibaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَكُمْ",
        "answer": "some of you",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "baʿḍakum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "(of) others",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "others",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُنَا",
        "answer": "some of us",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "baʿḍunā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "by others",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "bibaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَ",
        "answer": "some (of)",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "baʿḍa",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضًا",
        "answer": "(to) others",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "baʿḍan",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُ",
        "answer": "some (of)",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "baʿḍu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُ",
        "answer": "some (of)",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "baʿḍu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَكُمْ",
        "answer": "some of you",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "baʿḍakum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "others",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْتَةً",
        "answer": "suddenly",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baghtatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْتَةً",
        "answer": "suddenly",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "baghtatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْتَةً",
        "answer": "suddenly",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "baghtatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْغِي",
        "answer": "I (should) seek",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "abghī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبْتَغِيَ",
        "answer": "seek",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "tabtaghiya",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْتَغِي",
        "answer": "I seek",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "abtaghī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَغْيِهِمْ",
        "answer": "for their rebellion",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "bibaghyihim",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَاغٍ",
        "answer": "desiring",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "bāghin",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَقَرِ",
        "answer": "the cows",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-baqari",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَقَرِ",
        "answer": "the cows",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-baqari",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبُكْمٌ",
        "answer": "and dumb",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wabuk'mun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبْلِسُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) dumbfounded",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "mub'lisūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَغَ",
        "answer": "it reaches",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "balagha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَلَغْنَا",
        "answer": "and we have reached",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wabalaghnā",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْلُغَ",
        "answer": "he reaches",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yablugha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَالِغَةُ",
        "answer": "the conclusive",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "l-bālighatu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَبْلُوَكُمْ",
        "answer": "so that He may test you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "liyabluwakum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْنَاءَهُمُ",
        "answer": "their sons",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "abnāahumu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَنَاتٍ",
        "answer": "and daughters",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "wabanātin",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِينَ",
        "answer": "sons",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "banīna",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْوَابَ",
        "answer": "gates",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "abwāba",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِنُبَيِّنَهُ",
        "answer": "and that We (may) make it clear",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "walinubayyinahu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتَسْتَبِينَ",
        "answer": "so that becomes manifest",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "walitastabīna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِي",
        "answer": "between me",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "baynī",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and between you",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "wabaynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِي",
        "answer": "between me",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "baynī",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and between you",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "wabaynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(came) before",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "between you",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "baynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِنَا",
        "answer": "among us",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "bayninā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَةٍ",
        "answer": "clear proof",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "bayyinatin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَةٌ",
        "answer": "clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "bayyinatun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "490",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبِينُ",
        "answer": "(the) clear",
        "pcklId": "491",
        "tlit": "l-mubīnu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "Clear",
        "pcklId": "492",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "manifest",
        "pcklId": "493",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "open",
        "pcklId": "494",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَّبِعُ",
        "answer": "(do) I follow",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "attabiʿu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَّبِعُ",
        "answer": "I follow",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "attabiʿu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبِعْ",
        "answer": "Follow",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ittabiʿ",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّبِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they follow",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yattabiʿūna",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُونَ",
        "answer": "you follow",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿūna",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعْ",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿ",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَّبِعُوهُ",
        "answer": "so follow it",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "fa-ittabiʿūhu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَّبِعُوهُ",
        "answer": "so follow it",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "fa-ittabiʿūhu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "underneath them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "taḥtihim",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِ",
        "answer": "beneath",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "taḥti",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَكْتُمْ",
        "answer": "and you have left",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wataraktum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتْلُ",
        "answer": "I will recite",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "atlu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَمَّتْ",
        "answer": "And (has been) fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "watammat",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمَامًا",
        "answer": "completing (Our Favor)",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "tamāman",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "repents",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثْمَرَ",
        "answer": "it bears fruit",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "athmara",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثْمَرَ",
        "answer": "it bears fruit",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "athmara",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَرِهِ",
        "answer": "its fruit",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "thamarihi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَرِهِ",
        "answer": "its fruit",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "thamarihi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَانِيَةَ",
        "answer": "Eight",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "thamāniyata",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ith'nayni",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ith'nayni",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ith'nayni",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ith'nayni",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثْوَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your abode",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "mathwākum",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاجْتَبَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We chose them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-ij'tabaynāhum",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْحَدُونَ",
        "answer": "they reject",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yajḥadūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجَادِلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "and argue with you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yujādilūnaka",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُجَادِلُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "so that they dispute with you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "liyujādilūkum",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَرَحْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you committed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jaraḥtum",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَمُوا",
        "answer": "committed crimes",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ajramū",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the criminals",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُجْرِمِيهَا",
        "answer": "(of) its criminals",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "muj'rimīhā",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(who are) criminals",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "We reward",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُجْزَوْنَ",
        "answer": "you will be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tuj'zawna",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيُجْزَوْنَ",
        "answer": "they will be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "sayuj'zawna",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَجْزِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "He will recompense them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "sayajzīhim",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَجْزِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "He will recompense them",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "sayajzīhim",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their recompense",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "jazaynāhum",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنَجْزِي",
        "answer": "We will recompense",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "sanajzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجْزَىٰ",
        "answer": "he will be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yuj'zā",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and made",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We made",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We had made him",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnāhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَجَعَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "certainly We (would) have made him",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "lajaʿalnāhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "but We have placed",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْعَلْهُ",
        "answer": "He places him",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yajʿalhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْعَلُونَهُ",
        "answer": "You make it",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "tajʿalūnahu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and He has made",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "made",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلُوا",
        "answer": "And they make",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalū",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We have made you",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnāka",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We made",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We made",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We placed",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْعَلُ",
        "answer": "He places",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yajʿalu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "He makes",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "yajʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْعَلُ",
        "answer": "places",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yajʿalu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلُوا",
        "answer": "And they assign",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalū",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(has) made you",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "jaʿalakum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَجْمَعَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "Surely He will assemble you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "layajmaʿannakum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَجَمَعَهُمْ",
        "answer": "surely He (would) have gathered them",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "lajamaʿahum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْمَعِينَ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ajmaʿīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِجَنَاحَيْهِ",
        "answer": "with its wings ",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bijanāḥayhi",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّ",
        "answer": "covered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "janna",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنَّ",
        "answer": "jinn",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-jina",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجِنِّ",
        "answer": "and the jinn",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-jini",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنِّ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] jinn",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-jini",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنِّ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] jinn",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-jini",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "And gardens",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wajannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "gardens",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَهْدَ",
        "answer": "strongest",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "jahda",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَهْرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and what you make public",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wajahrakum",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَهْرَةً",
        "answer": "openly",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "jahratan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْهَلُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) ignorant",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yajhalūna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِجَهَالَةٍ",
        "answer": "in ignorance",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bijahālatin",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَاهِلِينَ",
        "answer": "the ignorant",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-jāhilīna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَجِيبُ",
        "answer": "respond",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yastajību",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "it came to them",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءُوكَ",
        "answer": "they come to you",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "jāūka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "jāathumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكَ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "jāaka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكَ",
        "answer": "come to you",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "jāaka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "brought",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْتُمُونَا",
        "answer": "you have come to Us",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "ji'tumūnā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "jāathum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْ",
        "answer": "it comes",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "jāat",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "jāathum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "(do) I like",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "uḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَبِّ",
        "answer": "(of) the grain",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-ḥabi",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبًّا",
        "answer": "grain ",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "ḥabban",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبَّةٍ",
        "answer": "a grain",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "ḥabbatin",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَحَبِطَ",
        "answer": "surely (would be) worthless",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "laḥabiṭa",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَاجَّهُ",
        "answer": "And argued with him",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waḥājjahu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتُحَاجُّونِّي",
        "answer": "Do you argue with me",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "atuḥājjūnnī",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُجَّتُنَا",
        "answer": "(is) Our argument",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ḥujjatunā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُجَّةُ",
        "answer": "(is) the argument ",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-ḥujatu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِجْرٌ",
        "answer": "forbidden",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ḥij'run",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَدِيثٍ",
        "answer": "a talk",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḥadīthin",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرْثِ",
        "answer": "the crops",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarthi",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَرْثٌ",
        "answer": "and crops",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "waḥarthun",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَجًا",
        "answer": "and constricted",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ḥarajan",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "He (has) forbidden",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُرِّمَتْ",
        "answer": "forbidden",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ḥurrimat",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَرَّمُوا",
        "answer": "and forbid",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "waḥarramū",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "He has forbidden",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "He (has) forbidden",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمْنَا",
        "answer": "We forbade",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ḥarramnā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمْنَا",
        "answer": "We forbade",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ḥarramnā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمْنَا",
        "answer": "we (would) have forbidden",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ḥarramnā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "prohibited",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "has prohibited",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "has (been) forbidden",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُحَرَّمٌ",
        "answer": "and forbidden",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "wamuḥarramun",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحَرَّمًا",
        "answer": "(anything) forbidden",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "muḥarraman",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَحْزُنُكَ",
        "answer": "grieves you",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "layaḥzunuka",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُسْبَانًا",
        "answer": "(for) reckoning",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "ḥus'bānan",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاسِبِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the Reckoners",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-ḥāsibīna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their account",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "ḥisābihim",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابِكَ",
        "answer": "your account",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "ḥisābika",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their account",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "ḥisābihim",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا حَسْرَتَنَا",
        "answer": "Oh! Our regret",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yāḥasratanā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنَ",
        "answer": "did good",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "aḥsana",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "(is) best",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَسَنَةِ",
        "answer": "with a good deed",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥasanati",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِحْسَانًا",
        "answer": "(be) good",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "iḥ'sānan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَحْشُرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "We will gather them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "naḥshuruhum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْشَرُونَ",
        "answer": "they will be gathered",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'sharūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْشَرُوا",
        "answer": "they will be gathered",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'sharū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحْشَرُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be gathered",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tuḥ'sharūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَشَرْنَا",
        "answer": "and We gathered",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waḥasharnā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْشُرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "He will gather them",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yaḥshuruhum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَصَادِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) its harvest",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥaṣādihi",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَافِظُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) guarding",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yuḥāfiẓūna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَفَظَةً",
        "answer": "guardians",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ḥafaẓatan",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَفِيظٍ",
        "answer": "a guardian",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "biḥafīẓin",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَفِيظًا",
        "answer": "a guardian",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ḥafīẓan",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَقُّ",
        "answer": "has more right",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "aḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقَّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "[the] True",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the truth",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the truth",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّ",
        "answer": "(with) true",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّهُ",
        "answer": "its due",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqahu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "by (legal) right",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمُونَ",
        "answer": "they judge",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yaḥkumūna",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكَمًا",
        "answer": "(as) judge",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "ḥakaman",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُكْمُ",
        "answer": "(is) the decision",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-ḥuk'mu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُكْمُ",
        "answer": "(is) the judgment",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-ḥuk'mu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحُكْمَ",
        "answer": "and the judgment",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥuk'ma",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "(All) the praises and thanks",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "al-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "And all praises and thanks",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْمِلُونَ",
        "answer": "will bear",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaḥmilūna",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمَلَتْ",
        "answer": "carried",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥamalat",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمُولَةً",
        "answer": "(are some for) burden",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ḥamūlatan",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمِيمٍ",
        "answer": "boiling water",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥamīmin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَنِيفًا",
        "answer": "(as) a true monotheist",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥanīfan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَنِيفًا",
        "answer": "a true monotheist",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḥanīfan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَوْلَهَا",
        "answer": "(are) around it",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ḥawlahā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَوَايَا",
        "answer": "the entrails",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ḥawāyā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "where",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْرَانَ",
        "answer": "confused",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥayrāna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَحَاقَ",
        "answer": "but surrounded",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faḥāqa",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَحْيَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We gave him life",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "fa-aḥyaynāhu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَّ",
        "answer": "the living",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaya",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيِّ",
        "answer": "the living",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayi",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيَاتُنَا",
        "answer": "our life",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "ḥayātunā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةُ",
        "answer": "(is) the life",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayatu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةُ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayatu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةُ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayatu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَحْيَايَ",
        "answer": "and my living",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "wamaḥyāya",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَبِيرُ",
        "answer": "the All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-khabīru",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَبِيرُ",
        "answer": "the All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-khabīru",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَبِيرُ",
        "answer": "the All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-khabīru",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَتَمَ",
        "answer": "and sealed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wakhatama",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرِجُوا",
        "answer": "Discharge",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "akhrijū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْرِجُ",
        "answer": "He brings forth",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "yukh'riju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخْرَجْنَا",
        "answer": "then We bring forth",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "fa-akhrajnā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخْرَجْنَا",
        "answer": "Then We bring forth",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "fa-akhrajnā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُخْرِجُ",
        "answer": "We bring forth",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "nukh'riju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتُخْرِجُوهُ",
        "answer": "then produce it",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "fatukh'rijūhu",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَارِجٍ",
        "answer": "he comes out",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "bikhārijin",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُخْرِجُ",
        "answer": "and brings forth",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "wamukh'riju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُصُونَ",
        "answer": "guess",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yakhruṣūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْرُصُونَ",
        "answer": "guess",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "takhruṣūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَرَقُوا",
        "answer": "and they falsely attribute",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wakharaqū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَزَائِنُ",
        "answer": "(are the) treasures",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khazāinu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسِرُوا",
        "answer": "have lost",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khasirū",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسِرُوا",
        "answer": "lost",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khasirū",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسِرَ",
        "answer": "incurred loss",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khasira",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسِرَ",
        "answer": "(are) lost",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "khasira",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَضِرًا",
        "answer": "green plant",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "khaḍiran",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُطُوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) footsteps",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khuṭuwāti",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْفُونَ",
        "answer": "conceal",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yukh'fūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُخْفُونَ",
        "answer": "and you conceal",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "watukh'fūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخُفْيَةً",
        "answer": "and secretly",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wakhuf'yatan",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِصَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) exclusively",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "khāliṣatun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْتَلَطَ",
        "answer": "(is) joined",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ikh'talaṭa",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْتَلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "differing",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "takhtalifūna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَخْلِفْ",
        "answer": "and grant succession",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wayastakhlif",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَائِفَ",
        "answer": "successors",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "khalāifa",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْتَلِفًا",
        "answer": "diverse",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "mukh'talifan",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "created you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "khalaqakum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We created you",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "khalaqnākum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَلَقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "though He has created them",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wakhalaqahum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَلَقَ",
        "answer": "and He created",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wakhalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِقُ",
        "answer": "(the) Creator",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "khāliqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِنْزِيرٍ",
        "answer": "(of) swine ",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khinzīrin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخُوضُونَ",
        "answer": "engage (in vain talks)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yakhūḍūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخُوضُوا",
        "answer": "they engage",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yakhūḍū",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْضِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their discourse ",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "khawḍihim",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَافُ",
        "answer": "[I] fear",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "akhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخَافُونَ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yakhāfūna",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَافُ",
        "answer": "(do) I fear",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "akhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَافُ",
        "answer": "could I fear",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "akhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَافُونَ",
        "answer": "you fear",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "takhāfūna",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوَّلْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We bestowed (on) you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khawwalnākum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "with good",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "bikhayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) best",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرُ",
        "answer": "(is the) best",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "khayru",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرًا",
        "answer": "any good",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "khayran",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَابَّةٍ",
        "answer": "any animal",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "dābbatin",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَابِرُ",
        "answer": "(the) remnant",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "dābiru",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَجَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(by) degrees",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "darajātin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَجَاتٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) degrees",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "darajātun",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَجَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(in) ranks",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "darajātin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِدْرَارًا",
        "answer": "showering abundantly",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "mid'rāran",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَسْتَ",
        "answer": "You have studied",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "darasta",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِرَاسَتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their study",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "dirāsatihim",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُدْرِكُهُ",
        "answer": "grasp Him",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tud'rikuhu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُدْرِكُ",
        "answer": "(can) grasp",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yud'riku",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "you call",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "you call",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "you call",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "tadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "call",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "you call",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "tadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَهُ",
        "answer": "you call Him",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "tadʿūnahu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنَدْعُو",
        "answer": "Shall we call",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "anadʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُونَهُ",
        "answer": "who call him",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yadʿūnahu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "they invoke",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَمًا",
        "answer": "blood",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "daman",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَانِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "hanging low",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "dāniyatun",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَلدَّارُ",
        "answer": "but the home",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "walalddāru",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَارُ",
        "answer": "(will be) home",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "dāru",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّارِ",
        "answer": "(a good) home",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-dāri",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "other than Him",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their religion",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "dīnahum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their religion",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "dīnahum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their religion",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "dīnahum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينًا",
        "answer": "a religion",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "dīnan",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرَأَ",
        "answer": "He produced",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "dhara-a",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذُرِّيَّاتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their descendents",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wadhurriyyātihim",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتِهِ",
        "answer": "his descendents",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatihi",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّةِ",
        "answer": "the descendants",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyati",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِرَ",
        "answer": "(is) mentioned",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "dhukira",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِرَ",
        "answer": "has been mentioned",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "dhukira",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُذْكَرِ",
        "answer": "has been mentioned",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yudh'kari",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they mention",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yadhkurūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِّرُوا",
        "answer": "they were reminded",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "dhukkirū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذَكِّرْ",
        "answer": "But remind",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "wadhakkir",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "you take heed",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "tatadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذَّكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "who take heed",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "yadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "remember",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "tadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِذُكُورِنَا",
        "answer": "for our males",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "lidhukūrinā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلذَّكَرَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(Are) the two males",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "āldhakarayni",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلذَّكَرَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(Is it) the two males",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "āldhakarayni",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذِّكْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the reminder",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "l-dhik'rā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(for) reminder",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "dhik'rā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "a reminder",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "dhik'rā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذُنُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "for their sins",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "bidhunūbihim",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُذْهِبْكُمْ",
        "answer": "He can take you away",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yudh'hib'kum",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَذُوقُوا",
        "answer": "So taste",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fadhūqū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَاقُوا",
        "answer": "they tasted",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "dhāqū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُذِيقَ",
        "answer": "and make (you) taste ",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wayudhīqa",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you (could) see",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you (could) see",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتَكُمْ",
        "answer": "Have you seen",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ara-aytakum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Have you seen",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ara-aytum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتَكُمْ",
        "answer": "Have you seen",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ara-aytakum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَيْتَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ra-ayta",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَاكَ",
        "answer": "[I] see you",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "arāka",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَىٰ",
        "answer": "he saw",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "raā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَى",
        "answer": "he saw",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "raā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَى",
        "answer": "he saw",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "raā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you (could) see",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "We see",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "narā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُرِي",
        "answer": "We show(ed)",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "nurī",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "in their Lord",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "birabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "(of) our Lord",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "by our Lord",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "warabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "Lord",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "rabbahum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّ",
        "answer": "to (the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "lirabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(is) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(is) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord ",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "(is) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "And your Lord",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "warabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "Your Lord",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their Lord",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "birabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(with) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "Lord",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبًّا",
        "answer": "(as) a Lord",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "rabban",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the Lord",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّجْسَ",
        "answer": "the filth",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-rij'sa",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجْسٌ",
        "answer": "(is) filth ",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "rij'sun",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "they will be returned",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْجِعُكُمْ",
        "answer": "will be your return",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "marjiʿukum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْجِعُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their return",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "marjiʿuhum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْجِعُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your return",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "marjiʿukum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلًا",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "rajulan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْجُلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your feet",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "arjulikum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِمَهُ",
        "answer": "He had Mercy on him",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "raḥimahu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْحَمُونَ",
        "answer": "receive mercy",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tur'ḥamūna",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْحَامُ",
        "answer": "(the) wombs",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "arḥāmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْحَامُ",
        "answer": "(the) wombs",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "arḥāmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَةَ",
        "answer": "the Mercy",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmata",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَةَ",
        "answer": "the Mercy",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmata",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) mercy",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmati",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) Mercy",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "raḥmatin",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "and mercy",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةٌ",
        "answer": "and a Mercy",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُرَدُّ",
        "answer": "were sent back",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "nuraddu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُدُّوا",
        "answer": "they were sent back",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ruddū",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُدُّوا",
        "answer": "they are returned",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ruddū",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُرَدُّ",
        "answer": "and we turn back",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wanuraddu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرَدُّ",
        "answer": "will be turned back",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yuraddu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُرْدُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "so that they may ruin them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "liyur'dūhum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقَهُمُ",
        "answer": "(bas been) provided (to) them",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "razaqahumu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقَكُمُ",
        "answer": "(has been) provided (to) you",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "razaqakumu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَرْزُقُكُمْ",
        "answer": "provide for you",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "narzuqukum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We sent",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent (Messengers)",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُرْسِلُ",
        "answer": "We send",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "nur'silu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُرْسِلُ",
        "answer": "and He sends",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wayur'silu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِسَالَتَهُ",
        "answer": "His Message",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "risālatahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرُسُلٍ",
        "answer": "Messengers",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "birusulin",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلٌ",
        "answer": "Messengers",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "rusulun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُنَا",
        "answer": "Our messengers",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "rusulunā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُ",
        "answer": "(to the) Messengers",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "rusulu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلٌ",
        "answer": "Messengers",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "rusulun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "478",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "479",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيَرْضَوْهُ",
        "answer": "and so that they may be pleased with it",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "waliyarḍawhu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَطْبٍ",
        "answer": "moist",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "raṭbin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَرْفَعُ",
        "answer": "We raise",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "narfaʿu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَفَعَ",
        "answer": "and raised",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "warafaʿa",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَرَاكِبًا",
        "answer": "thick clustered",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "mutarākiban",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالرُّمَّانَ",
        "answer": "and the pomegranates",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-rumāna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالرُّمَّانَ",
        "answer": "and the pomegranates",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-rumāna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "desiring",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "yurīdūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِدِ",
        "answer": "wants",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yuridi",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِدْ",
        "answer": "He wants",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "yurid",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَيْبَ",
        "answer": "doubt",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "rayba",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُخْرُفَ",
        "answer": "(with) decorative",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "zukh'rufa",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالزَّرْعَ",
        "answer": "and the crops",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-zarʿa",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزْعُمُونَ",
        "answer": "claim",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tazʿumūna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَعَمْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you claimed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "zaʿamtum",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزْعُمُونَ",
        "answer": "claim",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tazʿumūna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِزَعْمِهِمْ",
        "answer": "by their claim",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "bizaʿmihim",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِزَعْمِهِمْ",
        "answer": "by their claim",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "bizaʿmihim",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجِنَا",
        "answer": "our spouses",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "azwājinā",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجٍ",
        "answer": "pairs ",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "azwājin",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالزَّيْتُونَ",
        "answer": "and the olives",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-zaytūna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالزَّيْتُونَ",
        "answer": "and the olives",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-zaytūna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "and made fair-seeming",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wazayyana",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَيَّنَّا",
        "answer": "We have made fair-seeming",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "zayyannā",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُيِّنَ",
        "answer": "is made fair-seeming",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "zuyyina",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَيَّنَ",
        "answer": "made pleasing",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "zayyana",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْأَلُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I ask you",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "asalukum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسُبُّوا",
        "answer": "insult",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tasubbū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَسُبُّوا",
        "answer": "lest they insult",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fayasubbū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَهُ",
        "answer": "Glorified is He",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānahu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلُ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "sabīlu",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِهِ",
        "answer": "His way",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "sabīlihi",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّبُلَ",
        "answer": "the (other) paths",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-subula",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِهِ",
        "answer": "His path",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "sabīlihi",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِحْرٌ",
        "answer": "magic",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "siḥ'run",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَخِرُوا",
        "answer": "scoffed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sakhirū",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِرَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your secret",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "sirrakum",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْرَعُ",
        "answer": "(is) swiftest",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "asraʿu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَرِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) swift",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "sarīʿu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسْرِفُوا",
        "answer": "(be) extravagant",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tus'rifū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْرِفِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones who are extravagant",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-mus'rifīna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسَاطِيرُ",
        "answer": "(the) tales",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "asāṭīru",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْفُوحًا",
        "answer": "poured forth",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "masfūḥan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفَهًا",
        "answer": "(in) foolishness",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "safahan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْقُطُ",
        "answer": "falls",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tasquṭu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَكَنَ",
        "answer": "dwells",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sakana",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَكَنًا",
        "answer": "(for) rest",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "sakanan",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانًا",
        "answer": "any authority",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭānan",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْلَمَ",
        "answer": "submits (to Allah)",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "aslama",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنُسْلِمَ",
        "answer": "that we submit",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "linus'lima",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Peace",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "salāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّلَامِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] peace",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-salāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلَّمًا",
        "answer": "a ladder",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "sullaman",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْإِسْلَامِ",
        "answer": "to Islam",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "lil'is'lāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْلِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the ones who surrender (to Him)",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "l-mus'limīna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "listen",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَمِعُ",
        "answer": "listen",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "yastamiʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمْعَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hearing",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "samʿakum",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Hearer",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْمُ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "us'mu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْمُ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "us'mu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْمُ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "us'mu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْمَ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "is'ma",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "(rain from) the sky",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَمًّى",
        "answer": "specified",
        "pcklId": "377",
        "tlit": "musamman",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَمًّى",
        "answer": "specified",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "musamman",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاءَ",
        "answer": "Evil",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "sāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاءَ",
        "answer": "Evil",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "sāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءًا",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "sūan",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءَ",
        "answer": "(with) an evil",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "sūa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسَّيِّئَةِ",
        "answer": "with an evil deed",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "bil-sayi-ati",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةُ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿatu",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةُ",
        "answer": "the Hour ",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿatu",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَوِي",
        "answer": "be equal",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yastawī",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِيرُوا",
        "answer": "Travel",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sīrū",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَشَابِهٍ",
        "answer": "resembling",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "mutashābihin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَشَابِهًا",
        "answer": "similar",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mutashābihan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَشَابِهٍ",
        "answer": "similar",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "mutashābihin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُشْتَبِهًا",
        "answer": "resembling",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "mush'tabihan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُحُومَهُمَا",
        "answer": "their fat",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shuḥūmahumā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشُدَّهُ",
        "answer": "his maturity",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ashuddahu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدٌ",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "shadīdun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرَابٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) a drink",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "sharābun",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْرَحْ",
        "answer": "He expands",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yashraḥ",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "you associate (with Him)",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكُوا",
        "answer": "associated others with Allah",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ashrakū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "you associate (with Him)",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "tush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "associate partners (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "tush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "you associate (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "you associate",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you associate (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ashraktum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكْتُمْ",
        "answer": "have associated",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ashraktum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكُوا",
        "answer": "they (had) associated partners (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ashrakū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكُوا",
        "answer": "associated partners (with Him)",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ashrakū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكُوا",
        "answer": "associate partners (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ashrakū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكْنَا",
        "answer": "we (would) have associated partners (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ashraknā",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُشْرِكُوا",
        "answer": "associate",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "tush'rikū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاؤُكُمُ",
        "answer": "your partners",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "shurakāukumu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاءُ",
        "answer": "partners (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "shurakāu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاءَ",
        "answer": "partners ",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "shurakāa",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِشُرَكَائِنَا",
        "answer": "(is) for our partners",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "lishurakāinā",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِشُرَكَائِهِمْ",
        "answer": "for their partners",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "lishurakāihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَائِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their partners",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "shurakāihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاؤُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their partners ",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "shurakāuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) partners",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "shurakāu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرِيكَ",
        "answer": "partners",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "sharīka",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "those who associated others (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "(would) be the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "lamush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists ",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيَاطِينُ",
        "answer": "(by) the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-shayāṭīnu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيَاطِينَ",
        "answer": "the devils",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-shayāṭīna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانِ",
        "answer": "(of) Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيَاطِينَ",
        "answer": "devils",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "shayāṭīna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they perceive",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they perceive",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُشْعِرُكُمْ",
        "answer": "will make you perceive",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yush'ʿirukum",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَفِيعٌ",
        "answer": "any intercessor",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "shafīʿun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَفِيعٌ",
        "answer": "any intercessor",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "shafīʿun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُفَعَاءَكُمُ",
        "answer": "your intercessors",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "shufaʿāakumu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالشَّاكِرِينَ",
        "answer": "of those who are grateful",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "bil-shākirīna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّاكِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the grateful ones",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-shākirīna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّمْسَ",
        "answer": "the sun",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-shamsa",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّمْسَ",
        "answer": "and the sun",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-shamsa",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَمَلَتْ",
        "answer": "contains",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ish'tamalat",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَمَلَتْ",
        "answer": "contains",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ish'tamalat",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَشْهَدُونَ",
        "answer": "testify",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "latashhadūna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْهَدُ",
        "answer": "(do) I testify",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ashhadu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِدْنَا",
        "answer": "We bear witness",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "shahid'nā",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَشَهِدُوا",
        "answer": "and they will bear witness",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "washahidū",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْهَدُونَ",
        "answer": "testify",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yashhadūna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِدُوا",
        "answer": "they testify",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "shahidū",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْهَدْ",
        "answer": "testify",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tashhad",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهَادَةً",
        "answer": "(as) a testimony",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "shahādatan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّهَادَةِ",
        "answer": "and the seen",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "wal-shahādati",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Witness",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "shahīdun",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُهَدَاءَ",
        "answer": "witnesses",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "shuhadāa",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُهَدَاءَكُمُ",
        "answer": "your witnesses",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "shuhadāakumu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(had) willed",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَإِ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "yasha-i",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَأْ",
        "answer": "He wills ",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yasha",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yashāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "We will",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(had) willed",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "yashāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(had) willed",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَأْ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yasha",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(had) willed",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "we will",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "Had willed",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "He (had) willed",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "300",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "307",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "308",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٌ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "shayon",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِيَعًا",
        "answer": "(into) sects",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shiyaʿan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِيَعًا",
        "answer": "sects",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shiyaʿan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِصْبَاحِ",
        "answer": "(of) the daybreak",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-iṣ'bāḥi",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَبَرُوا",
        "answer": "but they were patient",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "faṣabarū",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابٌ",
        "answer": "companions",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābun",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَاحِبَةٌ",
        "answer": "a companion",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "ṣāḥibatun",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدْرَهُ",
        "answer": "his breast",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ṣadrahu",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدْرَهُ",
        "answer": "his breast",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṣadrahu",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصْدِفُونَ",
        "answer": "turn away",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaṣdifūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَدَفَ",
        "answer": "and turns away",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waṣadafa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصْدِفُونَ",
        "answer": "turn away",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaṣdifūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصْدِفُونَ",
        "answer": "turn away",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaṣdifūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِدْقًا",
        "answer": "(in) truth",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ṣid'qan",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَصَادِقُونَ",
        "answer": "[surely] are truthful",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "laṣādiqūna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَدِّقُ",
        "answer": "confirming",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "muṣaddiqu",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "a path",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطُ",
        "answer": "(is the) way",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭu",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطِي",
        "answer": "(is) My path",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭī",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "a path",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصْرَفْ",
        "answer": "is averted",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuṣ'raf",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُصَرِّفُ",
        "answer": "We explain",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "nuṣarrifu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُصَرِّفُ",
        "answer": "We explain",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "nuṣarrifu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُصَرِّفُ",
        "answer": "We explain",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "nuṣarrifu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصَّعَّدُ",
        "answer": "he (were) climbing",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaṣṣaʿʿadu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَغَارٌ",
        "answer": "a humiliation",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣaghārun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتَصْغَىٰ",
        "answer": "And so that incline",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "walitaṣghā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْلَحَ",
        "answer": "and reformed",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣlaḥa",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْلَحَ",
        "answer": "and reforms",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣlaḥa",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَلَاتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their prayers",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ṣalātihim",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَلَاتِي",
        "answer": "my prayer",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ṣalātī",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُمٌّ",
        "answer": "(are) deaf",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ṣummun",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْنَامًا",
        "answer": "idols",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aṣnāman",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيُصِيبُ",
        "answer": "Will afflict",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "sayuṣību",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّورِ",
        "answer": "the trumpet",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-ṣūri",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّأْنِ",
        "answer": "the sheep",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ḍani",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضُرُّنَا",
        "answer": "harms us",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yaḍurrunā",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اضْطُرِرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are compelled",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "uḍ'ṭurir'tum",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "اضْطُرَّ",
        "answer": "(is) compelled",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "uḍ'ṭurra",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِضُرٍّ",
        "answer": "with affliction",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "biḍurrin",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالضَّرَّاءِ",
        "answer": "and hardship",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "wal-ḍarāi",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَضَرَّعُوا",
        "answer": "they humbled themselves",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taḍarraʿū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَضَرَّعُونَ",
        "answer": "humble themselves",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yataḍarraʿūna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَضَرُّعًا",
        "answer": "humbly",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "taḍarruʿan",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَلَّ",
        "answer": "And lost",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "waḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَلْتُ",
        "answer": "I would go astray",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḍalaltu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَلَّ",
        "answer": "and is lost",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "waḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضِلُّ",
        "answer": "strays",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yaḍillu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "they have gone astray",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضْلِلْهُ",
        "answer": "He lets him go astray",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "yuḍ'lil'hu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضِلُّوكَ",
        "answer": "they will mislead you",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "yuḍillūka",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيُضِلُّونَ",
        "answer": "surely lead astray",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "layuḍillūna",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضِلَّهُ",
        "answer": "He lets him go astray",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "yuḍillahu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُضِلَّ",
        "answer": "to mislead",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "liyuḍilla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "error",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّالِّينَ",
        "answer": "who went astray",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "l-ḍālīna",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَيِّقًا",
        "answer": "tight",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ḍayyiqan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَطْرُدِ",
        "answer": "send away",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taṭrudi",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَطْرُدَهُمْ",
        "answer": "So were you to send them away",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fataṭrudahum",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطْعَمُهَا",
        "answer": "can eat them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaṭʿamuhā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطْعَمُهُ",
        "answer": "who eats it",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaṭʿamuhu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُطْعِمُ",
        "answer": "Who feeds",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yuṭ'ʿimu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُطْعَمُ",
        "answer": "He is fed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yuṭ'ʿamu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَاعِمٍ",
        "answer": "an eater",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ṭāʿimin",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُغْيَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their transgression",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ṭugh'yānihim",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَلْعِهَا",
        "answer": "its spathe",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṭalʿihā",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُطِعْ",
        "answer": "you obey",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "tuṭiʿ",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَطَعْتُمُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you obey them",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "aṭaʿtumūhum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَطَعْتَ",
        "answer": "you are able",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "is'taṭaʿta",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفَتَيْنِ",
        "answer": "the two groups",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ṭāifatayni",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطِيرُ",
        "answer": "(that) flies",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaṭīru",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِرٍ",
        "answer": "a bird",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ṭāirin",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "طِينٍ",
        "answer": "clay",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṭīnin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُفُرٍ",
        "answer": "claws",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ẓufurin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "did wrong",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُظْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) wronged",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yuẓ'lamūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more unjust",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more unjust",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more unjust",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more unjust",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِظُلْمٍ",
        "answer": "with wrong",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "biẓul'min",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِظُلْمٍ",
        "answer": "for (their) wrongdoing",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "biẓul'min",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظُّلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "the darkness[es]",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "l-ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظُّلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "the darkness[es]",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "l-ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "the darkness[es]",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "darkness[es]",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "the darkness[es]",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظُّلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "the darknesses",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "l-ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers ",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "of the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "bil-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoing",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّنَّ",
        "answer": "[the] assumption",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-ẓana",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّنَّ",
        "answer": "the assumption",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-ẓana",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَهَرَ",
        "answer": "(is) apparent",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ẓahara",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُهُورِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their backs",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ẓuhūrihim",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُهُورِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your backs",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ẓuhūrikum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُهُورُهَا",
        "answer": "(are) their backs",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ẓuhūruhā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُهُورُهُمَا",
        "answer": "their backs",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ẓuhūruhumā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَاهِرَ",
        "answer": "open",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ẓāhira",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْبُدَ",
        "answer": "I worship",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "aʿbuda",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْبُدُوهُ",
        "answer": "so worship Him",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fa-uʿ'budūhu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "His slaves",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "His slaves",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "His slaves",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمُعْجِزِينَ",
        "answer": "escape (it)",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "bimuʿ'jizīna",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَعْجِلُونَ",
        "answer": "you seek to hasten",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tastaʿjilūna",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَعْجِلُونَ",
        "answer": "you seek to hasten",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tastaʿjilūna",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْدِلُونَ",
        "answer": "equate others with Him",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaʿdilūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْدِلْ",
        "answer": "it offers ransom ",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "taʿdil",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْدِلُونَ",
        "answer": "set up equals",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaʿdilūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْدِلُوا",
        "answer": "then be just",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'dilū",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدْلٍ",
        "answer": "ransom",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ʿadlin",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدْلًا",
        "answer": "and justice",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "waʿadlan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوًّا",
        "answer": "an enemy ",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwan",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدْوًا",
        "answer": "(in) enmity",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "ʿadwan",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمُعْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "of the transgressors",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "bil-muʿ'tadīna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادٍ",
        "answer": "transgressing",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "ʿādin",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَ",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابُ",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابُ",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "and a punishment",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "waʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَ",
        "answer": "(with) punishment",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "and a punishment",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "waʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْرُوشَاتٍ",
        "answer": "trellised",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "maʿrūshātin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْرُوشَاتٍ",
        "answer": "trellised",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "maʿrūshātin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَعْرِضْ",
        "answer": "then turn away",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fa-aʿriḍ",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْرِضْ",
        "answer": "and turn away",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿriḍ",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِعْرَاضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their aversion",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "iʿ'rāḍuhum",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْرِضِينَ",
        "answer": "turning away",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "muʿ'riḍīna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْرِفُونَهُ",
        "answer": "they recognize him",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaʿrifūnahu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْرِفُونَ",
        "answer": "they recognize",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yaʿrifūna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزِ",
        "answer": "(of) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشْرُ",
        "answer": "(is) ten (times)",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ʿashru",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا مَعْشَرَ",
        "answer": "(and will say), \"O assembly",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yāmaʿshara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا مَعْشَرَ",
        "answer": "O assembly",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yāmaʿshara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَشِيِّ",
        "answer": "and the evening",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿashiyi",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَصَيْتُ",
        "answer": "I disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿaṣaytu",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَظْمٍ",
        "answer": "with the bone",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "biʿaẓmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٍ",
        "answer": "Mighty",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "(the) end",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "(in) the end",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِقَابِ",
        "answer": "(in) the punishment",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiqābi",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْقَابِنَا",
        "answer": "our heels",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "aʿqābinā",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) you reason",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "use reason",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "He knows",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "and He knows",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "wayaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "We know",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "naʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(that) I know",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُهَا",
        "answer": "knows them",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamuhā",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "And He knows",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "wayaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُهَا",
        "answer": "He knows it",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamuhā",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "and He knows",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "wayaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you will know",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "knew",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "taʿlamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) know",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "who know",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you will know",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعُلِّمْتُمْ",
        "answer": "And you were taught",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "waʿullim'tum",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "most knowing",
        "pcklId": "433",
        "tlit": "bi-aʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "434",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows best",
        "pcklId": "435",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "436",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "437",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows best",
        "pcklId": "438",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "489",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "490",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "491",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the worlds",
        "pcklId": "492",
        "tlit": "lil'ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "493",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمًا",
        "answer": "(in) knowledge",
        "pcklId": "569",
        "tlit": "ʿil'man",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "knowledge",
        "pcklId": "570",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "knowledge",
        "pcklId": "571",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "knowledge",
        "pcklId": "572",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "knowledge",
        "pcklId": "573",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "with knowledge",
        "pcklId": "574",
        "tlit": "biʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "knowledge",
        "pcklId": "575",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "any knowledge",
        "pcklId": "576",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "679",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "680",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمِ",
        "answer": "the All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "681",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "682",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "683",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "684",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "791",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِمُ",
        "answer": "(He is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "824",
        "tlit": "ʿālimu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَعَالَىٰ",
        "answer": "and Exalted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wataʿālā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعَالَوْا",
        "answer": "Come",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "taʿālaw",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلَ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "ʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "doing",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "they did",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "they do",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْمَلُوا",
        "answer": "Work",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "iʿ'malū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their deed",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "ʿamalahum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامِلٌ",
        "answer": "a worker",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "ʿāmilun",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَهُونَ",
        "answer": "wandering blindly",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaʿmahūna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِيَ",
        "answer": "(is) blind",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿamiya",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْمَىٰ",
        "answer": "the blind",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-aʿmā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْنَابٍ",
        "answer": "grapes",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "aʿnābin",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَهُ",
        "answer": "with Him",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ʿindahu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِي",
        "answer": "(that) with me",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ʿindī",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِي",
        "answer": "I have",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ʿindī",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِي",
        "answer": "(were) with me",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ʿindī",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِنْدَهُ",
        "answer": "And with Him",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "waʿindahu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(are) with",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَكُمْ",
        "answer": "with you",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ʿindakum",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِعَهْدِ",
        "answer": "And (the) Covenant",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wabiʿahdi",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعَادُوا",
        "answer": "certainly they (would) return",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "laʿādū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْغَدَاةِ",
        "answer": "in the morning",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "bil-ghadati",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَرَّتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "and deluded them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wagharrathumu",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَرَّتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "And deluded them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wagharrathumu",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُرُورًا",
        "answer": "(in) deception",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ghurūran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَغَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "[certainly], Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "laghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَافِلُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) unaware",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ghāfilūna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَافِلٍ",
        "answer": "unaware",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "bighāfilin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَغَافِلِينَ",
        "answer": "certainly unaware",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "laghāfilīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَمَرَاتِ",
        "answer": "agonies",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ghamarāti",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْغَنَمِ",
        "answer": "and the sheep",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-ghanami",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَنِيُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the Self-Sufficient",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-ghaniyu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبَ",
        "answer": "the unseen",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-ghayba",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغَيْرَ",
        "answer": "Is it other than",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "aghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغَيْرَ",
        "answer": "is it other",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "aghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ghayru",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرِهِ",
        "answer": "other than it",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ghayrihi",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَيْرَ",
        "answer": "and not",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "waghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَغَيْرَ",
        "answer": "Then is (it) other than",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "afaghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَيْرَ",
        "answer": "and other than",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "waghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَيْرَ",
        "answer": "and other than",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "waghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "to other than",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "lighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغَيْرَ",
        "answer": "Is (it) other than",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "aghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفْئِدَتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "afidatahum",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفْئِدَةُ",
        "answer": "hearts",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "afidatu",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَحْنَا",
        "answer": "We opened",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fataḥnā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَفَاتِحُ",
        "answer": "(are the) keys",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "mafātiḥu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَنَّا",
        "answer": "We try",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fatannā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَتُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(for) them a plea",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "fit'natuhum",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوَاحِشَ",
        "answer": "[the] immoralities",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-fawāḥisha",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِحُوا",
        "answer": "they rejoiced",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fariḥū",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُرَادَىٰ",
        "answer": "alone",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "furādā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَرْشًا",
        "answer": "and (some for) meat",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wafarshan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَّطْنَا",
        "answer": "we neglected",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "farraṭnā",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَّطْنَا",
        "answer": "We have neglected",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "farraṭnā",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفَرِّطُونَ",
        "answer": "fail",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yufarriṭūna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَّقُوا",
        "answer": "divide",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "farraqū",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَفَرَّقَ",
        "answer": "then they will separate",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fatafarraqa",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَرِيقَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(of) the two parties",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-farīqayni",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "invents",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "if'tarā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "invent",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaftarūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "invents",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "if'tarā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "they invent",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yaftarūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "they invent",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yaftarūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "invent",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yaftarūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "invents",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "if'tarā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتِرَاءً",
        "answer": "(as) an invention",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "if'tirāan",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتِرَاءً",
        "answer": "inventing (lies)",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "if'tirāan",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْسُقُونَ",
        "answer": "defiantly disobey",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yafsuqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَفِسْقٌ",
        "answer": "grave disobedience",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "lafis'qun",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِسْقًا",
        "answer": "(it be) disobedience",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fis'qan",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفَصِّلُ",
        "answer": "We explain",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "nufaṣṣilu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have made clear",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "faṣṣalnā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have made clear",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "faṣṣalnā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَّلَ",
        "answer": "He (has) explained in detail",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "faṣṣala",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have detailed",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "faṣṣalnā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاصِلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the Deciders",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-fāṣilīna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَفْصِيلًا",
        "answer": "and an explanation",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "watafṣīlan",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُفَصَّلًا",
        "answer": "explained in detail",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "mufaṣṣalan",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We preferred",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "faḍḍalnā",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَطَرَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faṭara",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاطِرِ",
        "answer": "Creator",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "fāṭiri",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلُوهُ",
        "answer": "they (would) have done it",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "faʿalūhu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلُوهُ",
        "answer": "(would) they have done so",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "faʿalūhu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yafʿalūna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُوهُ",
        "answer": "they understand it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yafqahūhu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yafqahūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) understand",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yafqahūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَفَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "you give thought",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tatafakkarūna",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفْلِحُ",
        "answer": "will be successful",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yuf'liḥu",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفْلِحُ",
        "answer": "succeed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yuf'liḥu",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالِقُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Cleaver",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fāliqu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالِقُ",
        "answer": "(He is the) Cleaver",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fāliqu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوْزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the success",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-fawzu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقِكُمْ",
        "answer": "above you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fawqikum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَ",
        "answer": "over",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "fawqa",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَ",
        "answer": "over",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "fawqa",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَ",
        "answer": "above",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "fawqa",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِنَا",
        "answer": "before us",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "qablinā",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُبُلًا",
        "answer": "face to face",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "qubulan",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتَلُوا",
        "answer": "killed",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "qatalū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلُوا",
        "answer": "kill",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "taqtulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلُوا",
        "answer": "kill",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "taqtulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتْلَ",
        "answer": "(the) killing",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "qatla",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَرُوا",
        "answer": "they appraised",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "qadarū",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدْرِهِ",
        "answer": "[of his] appraisal",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "qadrihi",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَادِرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Able",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "qādirun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَادِرُ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Capable",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "l-qādiru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْدِيرُ",
        "answer": "(is the) ordaining",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "taqdīru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْتَدِهْ",
        "answer": "you follow",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "iq'tadih",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنُ",
        "answer": "[the] Quran",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-qur'ānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "go near",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "taqrabū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "go near",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "taqrabū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "a near relative",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "qur'bā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقَرٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) a fixed time",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "mus'taqarrun",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمُسْتَقَرٌّ",
        "answer": "so (there is) a place of dwelling",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "famus'taqarrun",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِرْطَاسٍ",
        "answer": "a parchment",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qir'ṭāsin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرَاطِيسَ",
        "answer": "(into) parchments",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "qarāṭīsa",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيَقْتَرِفُوا",
        "answer": "and so that they may commit",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waliyaqtarifū",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْتَرِفُونَ",
        "answer": "commit",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaqtarifūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُقْتَرِفُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) committing",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "muq'tarifūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْنٍ",
        "answer": "generations",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qarnin",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْنًا",
        "answer": "generations",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "qarnan",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) the cities",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "city",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the cities",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقِسْطِ",
        "answer": "with justice",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "bil-qis'ṭi",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقْسَمُوا",
        "answer": "And they swear",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-aqsamū",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَسَتْ",
        "answer": "became hardened",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "qasat",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُصُّ",
        "answer": "He relates",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaquṣṣu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُصُّونَ",
        "answer": "relating",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaquṣṣūna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَضَىٰ",
        "answer": "He decreed",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "qaḍā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقُضِيَ",
        "answer": "surely (would) have been decided",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "laquḍiya",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقُضِيَ",
        "answer": "surely would have been decided",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "laquḍiya",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُقْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "so that is fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "liyuq'ḍā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُطِعَ",
        "answer": "So was cut off",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "faquṭiʿa",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقَطَّعَ",
        "answer": "have been severed (bonds)",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "taqaṭṭaʿa",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْعُدْ",
        "answer": "sit",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taqʿud",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُقَلِّبُ",
        "answer": "And We will turn",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wanuqallibu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hearts",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "qulūbikum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَمَرَ",
        "answer": "the moon",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-qamara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرَ",
        "answer": "and the moon",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-qamara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِنْوَانٌ",
        "answer": "clusters of dates",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qin'wānun",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَاهِرُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Subjugator",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-qāhiru",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَاهِرُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Subjugator",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-qāhiru",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَالَ",
        "answer": "surely (would) have said",
        "pcklId": "298",
        "tlit": "laqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "299",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "300",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "307",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "308",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقُولُ",
        "answer": "We will say",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "naqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "then they (will) say",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "faqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He (will) say",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They will say",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He (will) say",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "324",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقُولُ",
        "answer": "(do) I say",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "aqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقُولُ",
        "answer": "I say",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "aqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "that they say",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "liyaqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْ",
        "answer": "then say",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "faqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "332",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "333",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "334",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "He says",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "347",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "351",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "taqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "that they (may) say",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "waliyaqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And will say",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He will say",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They will say",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and they say",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "faqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْ",
        "answer": "then say",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "tlit": "faqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "Will say",
        "pcklId": "371",
        "tlit": "sayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "373",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "374",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you speak",
        "pcklId": "376",
        "tlit": "qul'tum",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "377",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلُهُ",
        "answer": "His word",
        "pcklId": "1643",
        "tlit": "qawluhu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "[the] speech",
        "pcklId": "1644",
        "tlit": "l-qawli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "establish",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "aqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمُ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "l-qawmu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمُكَ",
        "answer": "your people",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "qawmuka",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَوْمَكَ",
        "answer": "and your people",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "waqawmaka",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمُهُ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "qawmuhu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "(to) a people",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) people",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "qawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "505",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيَمًا",
        "answer": "right",
        "pcklId": "563",
        "tlit": "qiyaman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمًا",
        "answer": "straight",
        "pcklId": "623",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمًا",
        "answer": "straight",
        "pcklId": "624",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "(the) straight",
        "pcklId": "654",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "straight",
        "pcklId": "655",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "straight ",
        "pcklId": "656",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبُرَ",
        "answer": "difficult",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kabura",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَكْبِرُونَ",
        "answer": "being arrogant",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "tastakbirūna",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "(is) greatest",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "greater",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكَابِرَ",
        "answer": "greatest",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "akābira",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبَ",
        "answer": "He has decreed",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "kataba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبَ",
        "answer": "(Has) Prescribed",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "kataba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابًا",
        "answer": "a written Scripture",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "kitāban",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٍ",
        "answer": "a Record",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "kitābin",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a Book",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "kitābun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a Book",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "kitābun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابُ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-kitābu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابُ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-kitābu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَكْثَرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have (misled) many",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "is'takthartum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "aktharahum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "aktharahum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَ",
        "answer": "most",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "akthara",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "much (of it)",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكَثِيرٍ",
        "answer": "to many",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "likathīrin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَبُوا",
        "answer": "they lied",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "they denied",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "rejects",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُكَذِّبَ",
        "answer": "we would deny",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "nukadhiba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَذِّبُونَكَ",
        "answer": "deny you",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yukadhibūnaka",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُذِّبَتْ",
        "answer": "were rejected",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "kudhibat",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُذِّبُوا",
        "answer": "they were rejected",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "kudhibū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "rejected",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَذَّبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "while you deny",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wakadhabtum",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "But denied",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wakadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوكَ",
        "answer": "they deny you",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "kadhabūka",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "denies",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِبًا",
        "answer": "a lie",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "kadhiban",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِبًا",
        "answer": "a lie",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "kadhiban",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِبًا",
        "answer": "a lie",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "kadhiban",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَاذِبُونَ",
        "answer": "certainly are liars",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "lakādhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُكَذِّبِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the rejecters",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "l-mukadhibīna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرْبٍ",
        "answer": "distress",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "karbin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "you earn",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "taksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَتْ",
        "answer": "it (has) earned",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "kasabat",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبُوا",
        "answer": "they earned",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "kasabū",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَتْ",
        "answer": "earned",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "kasabat",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْسِبُ",
        "answer": "earns",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "taksibu",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَكْشِفُ",
        "answer": "and He would remove",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fayakshifu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاشِفَ",
        "answer": "remover",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "kāshifa",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْفُرُونَ",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "takfurūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرُونَ",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "yakfurūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرْ",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "yakfur",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "bikāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "to the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "lil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "425",
        "tlit": "kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُكَلِّفُ",
        "answer": "We burden",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nukallifu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) every",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "For every",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "likulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلًّا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "kullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "all (were)",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلًّا",
        "answer": "and all",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wakullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) every",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "(is) of every",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) every",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "to every",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "likulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "for every",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "likulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِكُلٍّ",
        "answer": "And for all",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "walikullin",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "of every",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "likulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) every",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَلَّمَهُمُ",
        "answer": "and spoken to them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wakallamahumu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكَلِمَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) words",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "likalimāti",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكَلِمَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His words",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "likalimātihi",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَتُ",
        "answer": "(the) word",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "kalimatu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكِنَّةً",
        "answer": "coverings",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "akinnatan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَوْكَبًا",
        "answer": "a star",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kawkaban",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they are",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكُونَ",
        "answer": "I be",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "akūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "takūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُنْ",
        "answer": "will be",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "takun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we were",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَكُونَ",
        "answer": "and we would be",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "wanakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "takūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَكُونَ",
        "answer": "then you would be",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "fatakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely we will be",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "lanakūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "298",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْ",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "299",
        "tlit": "kun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَكُونُ",
        "answer": "and it is",
        "pcklId": "300",
        "tlit": "fayakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيَكُونَ",
        "answer": "so that he would be",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "waliyakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "I will surely be",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "la-akūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "and you were",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "wakuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "307",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُ",
        "answer": "can be",
        "pcklId": "308",
        "tlit": "yakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُنْ",
        "answer": "(there) is",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "takun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "takūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "(of what) they used to",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُنْ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "yakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُ",
        "answer": "will have",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "takūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "324",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُنْ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "yakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they are",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "were you",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونَ",
        "answer": "it be",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "yakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he is",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we were",
        "pcklId": "332",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "surely we (would) have been",
        "pcklId": "333",
        "tlit": "lakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "334",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُنْ",
        "answer": "(if) it had",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "takun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and become",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he was",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانَتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your position",
        "pcklId": "1385",
        "tlit": "makānatikum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَيْفَ",
        "answer": "And how",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wakayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَيْلَ",
        "answer": "[the] measure",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-kayla",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَلَبَسْنَا",
        "answer": "and certainly We (would) have obscured",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "walalabasnā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْبِسُونَ",
        "answer": "they are obscuring",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yalbisūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْبِسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(to) confuse you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yalbisakum",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْبِسُوا",
        "answer": "mix",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yalbisū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيَلْبِسُوا",
        "answer": "and that they make confusing",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waliyalbisū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَحْمَ",
        "answer": "(the) flesh",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "laḥma",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّطِيفُ",
        "answer": "the All-Subtle",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-laṭīfu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْعَبُونَ",
        "answer": "playing",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yalʿabūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعِبٌ",
        "answer": "a play",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "laʿibun",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعِبًا",
        "answer": "(as) a play",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "laʿiban",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِلِقَاءِ",
        "answer": "in (the) meeting",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "biliqāi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَاءَ",
        "answer": "(of the) meeting",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "liqāa",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِلِقَاءِ",
        "answer": "in (the) meeting",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "biliqāi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَمَسُوهُ",
        "answer": "and they touched it",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "falamasūhu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَلُمَّ",
        "answer": "Bring forward",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "halumma",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَهْوٌ",
        "answer": "and amusement",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "walahwun",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَهْوًا",
        "answer": "and amusement",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "walahwan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is not",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "alaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "is not",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "alaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَسْتُ",
        "answer": "I am not",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "lastu",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسُوا",
        "answer": "who are not",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "laysū",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَسْتَ",
        "answer": "you are not",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "lasta",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "by the night",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "bi-al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلُ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "al-laylu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَمْتَعَ",
        "answer": "profited",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "is'tamtaʿa",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَ",
        "answer": "like",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "mith'la",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَ",
        "answer": "like",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "mith'la",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَهَا",
        "answer": "the like of it",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "mith'lahā",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلُهُ",
        "answer": "[similar to him]",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "mathaluhu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْثَالِهَا",
        "answer": "the like of it",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "amthālihā",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْثَالُكُمْ",
        "answer": "like you",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "amthālukum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "marratin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "marratin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "doubt",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tamtarūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُمْتَرِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones who doubt",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-mum'tarīna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْسَسْكَ",
        "answer": "touches you",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yamsaska",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْسَسْكَ",
        "answer": "He touches you",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yamsaska",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمَسُّهُمُ",
        "answer": "will touch them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yamassuhumu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْشِي",
        "answer": "he walks",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yamshī",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَعْزِ",
        "answer": "the goats",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-maʿzi",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَمْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "so that they plot",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "liyamkurū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they plot",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yamkurūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "plot",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yamkurūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَّنَّاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We had established them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "makkannāhum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُمَكِّنْ",
        "answer": "We (have) established",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "numakkin",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِمْلَاقٍ",
        "answer": "poverty",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "im'lāqin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Dominion",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "l-mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكٌ",
        "answer": "an Angel",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "malakun",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكًا",
        "answer": "an Angel",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "malakan",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكًا",
        "answer": "an Angel",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "malakan",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكٌ",
        "answer": "an Angel",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "malakun",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَلَائِكَةُ",
        "answer": "while the Angels",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "wal-malāikatu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةَ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "l-malāikata",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةُ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "l-malāikatu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكُوتَ",
        "answer": "the kingdom",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "malakūta",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِلَّةَ",
        "answer": "religion",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "millata",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَّ",
        "answer": "(whom has been) favored",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "manna",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَمَاتِي",
        "answer": "and my dying",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "wamamātī",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتُ",
        "answer": "the death",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-mawtu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] death",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-mawti",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَيْتًا",
        "answer": "dead",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "maytan",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "But the dead ",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "wal-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَيِّتِ",
        "answer": "the dead",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "l-mayiti",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَيِّتِ",
        "answer": "the dead",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "l-mayiti",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "the dead",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "l-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَيْتَةً",
        "answer": "(born) dead",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "maytatan",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَيْتَةً",
        "answer": "dead",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "maytatan",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَالَ",
        "answer": "wealth",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "māla",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءً",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "māan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْأَوْنَ",
        "answer": "and they keep away",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayanawna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَبِّئُكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will inform you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yunabbi-ukum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُنَبِّئُهُمْ",
        "answer": "then He will inform them",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fayunabbi-uhum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبِّئُونِي",
        "answer": "Inform me",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "nabbiūnī",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَبِّئُهُمْ",
        "answer": "He will inform them",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yunabbi-uhum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُنَبِّئُكُمْ",
        "answer": "then He will inform you",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fayunabbi-ukum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْبَاءُ",
        "answer": "news",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "anbāu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَإِ",
        "answer": "(the) news",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "naba-i",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَإٍ",
        "answer": "news",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "naba-in",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنُّبُوَّةَ",
        "answer": "and the Prophethood",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "wal-nubuwata",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبِيٍّ",
        "answer": "Prophet",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "nabiyyin",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَاتَ",
        "answer": "vegetation",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "nabāta",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّجُومَ",
        "answer": "the stars",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-nujūma",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَجِّيكُمْ",
        "answer": "saves you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yunajjīkum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَجِّيكُمْ",
        "answer": "saves you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yunajjīkum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْجَانَا",
        "answer": "He saves us",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "anjānā",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّخْلِ",
        "answer": "the date-palm",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-nakhli",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّخْلَ",
        "answer": "and the date-palm",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-nakhla",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأُنْذِرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "that I may warn you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "li-undhirakum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْذِرْ",
        "answer": "And warn",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-andhir",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتُنْذِرَ",
        "answer": "so that you may warn",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "walitundhira",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُنْذِرُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and warning you",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wayundhirūnakum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُنْذِرِينَ",
        "answer": "and (as) warners",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "wamundhirīna",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We (had) sent down",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "nazzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُزِّلَ",
        "answer": "sent down",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "nuzzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزِّلَ",
        "answer": "send down",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yunazzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزِّلْ",
        "answer": "did He send down",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yunazzil",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "[We] sent down",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "nazzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "sent down",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We (had) sent down",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "revealed",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "revealed",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have revealed it",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "anzalnāhu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأُنْزِلُ",
        "answer": "I will reveal",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "sa-unzilu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "(has been) revealed",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "sends down",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have revealed it ",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "anzalnāhu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنَزَّلٌ",
        "answer": "(is) sent down",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "munazzalun",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُسُكِي",
        "answer": "and my rites of sacrifice",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wanusukī",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَنْسَوْنَ",
        "answer": "and you will forget",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "watansawna",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسُوا",
        "answer": "they forgot",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "nasū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْسِيَنَّكَ",
        "answer": "causes you to forget",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yunsiyannaka",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْشَأْنَا",
        "answer": "and We raised",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-anshanā",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْشَأَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(has) produced you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ansha-akum",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْشَأَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He raised you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ansha-akum",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْشَأَ",
        "answer": "produced",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ansha-a",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيبًا",
        "answer": "a share",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "naṣīban",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرُنَا",
        "answer": "Our help",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "naṣrunā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرُوا",
        "answer": "see",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "unẓurū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْ",
        "answer": "Look",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْ",
        "answer": "See",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْ",
        "answer": "See",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرُوا",
        "answer": "Look",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "unẓurū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they waiting",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْظَرُونَ",
        "answer": "respite would have been granted to them",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "yunẓarūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْتَظِرُوا",
        "answer": "Wait",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "intaẓirū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْتَظِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) those who wait",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "muntaẓirūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَنْعَامِ",
        "answer": "and the cattle",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "wal-anʿāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَامٌ",
        "answer": "(are) cattle",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "anʿāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْعَامٌ",
        "answer": "And cattle",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "wa-anʿāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْعَامٌ",
        "answer": "and cattle",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "wa-anʿāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْعَامِ",
        "answer": "cattle",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-anʿāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْعَامِ",
        "answer": "the cattle",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-anʿāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفَخُ",
        "answer": "will be blown",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yunfakhu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "Himself",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "nafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "Himself",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "nafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٌ",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "nafsun",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمُ",
        "answer": "your souls",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "anfusakumu",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلِنَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "then (it is) for his soul",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "falinafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "against themselves",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "bi-anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِنَا",
        "answer": "ourselves",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "anfusinā",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّفْسَ",
        "answer": "the soul",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "l-nafsa",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسًا",
        "answer": "any soul",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "nafsan",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسًا",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "nafsan",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "soul",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْفَعُنَا",
        "answer": "benefits us",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yanfaʿunā",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْفَعُ",
        "answer": "will benefit",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yanfaʿu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفَقًا",
        "answer": "a tunnel",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "nafaqan",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "and the day",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالنَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "by the day",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "bil-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارَ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-anhāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْهَوْنَ",
        "answer": "forbid (others)",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yanhawna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُهُوا",
        "answer": "they were forbidden",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "nuhū",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُهِيتُ",
        "answer": "[I] am forbidden",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "nuhītu",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارُ",
        "answer": "The Fire",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-nāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنُّورَ",
        "answer": "and the light",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "wal-nūra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورًا",
        "answer": "(as) a light",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "nūran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورًا",
        "answer": "light",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "nūran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for the people",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّوَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the date-seed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-nawā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَانَا",
        "answer": "(has) guided us",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "hadānā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِنِي",
        "answer": "guide me",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yahdinī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَانِ",
        "answer": "He has guided me",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "hadāni",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We guided",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "hadaynā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We guided",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "hadaynā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهَدَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We guided them",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wahadaynāhum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "He guides",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَى",
        "answer": "(have been) guided",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "hadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِيَهُ",
        "answer": "He guides him ",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yahdiyahu",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَهَدَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "surely He (would) have guided you",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "lahadākum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَانِي",
        "answer": "has guided me",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "hadānī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَهْتَدُوا",
        "answer": "that you may guide yourselves",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "litahtadū",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْدَىٰ",
        "answer": "better guided",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "ahdā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "the guidance",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَى",
        "answer": "the guidance",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدَى",
        "answer": "(the) Guidance",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) the Guidance",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدَى",
        "answer": "(is the) Guidance",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبِهُدَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "so of their guidance",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "fabihudāhumu",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهُدًى",
        "answer": "and guidance",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "wahudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهُدًى",
        "answer": "and a guidance",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "wahudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهُدًى",
        "answer": "and a Guidance",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "wahudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُهْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "the guided-ones",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "l-muh'tadīna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) rightly guided",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "muh'tadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمُهْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "of the guided-ones",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "bil-muh'tadīna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "guided-ones",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "muh'tadīna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَهْزِئُونَ",
        "answer": "mock",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yastahziūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتُهْزِئَ",
        "answer": "were mocked",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "us'tuh'zi-a",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَهْزِئُونَ",
        "answer": "mock",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yastahziūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We destroyed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ahlaknā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَهْلَكْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "Then We destroyed them",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fa-ahlaknāhum",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُهْلِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they destroy",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yuh'likūna",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُهْلَكُ",
        "answer": "(any) be destroyed",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yuh'laku",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْلِكَ",
        "answer": "one who destroys",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "muh'lika",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُهِلَّ",
        "answer": "[is] dedicated",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "uhilla",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَادُوا",
        "answer": "are Jews",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "hādū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُونِ",
        "answer": "humiliating",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-hūni",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَهْوَتْهُ",
        "answer": "whom (has been) enticed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "is'tahwathu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْوَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your (vain) desires",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ahwāakum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَهْوَائِهِمْ",
        "answer": "by their (vain) desires",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "bi-ahwāihim",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْوَاءَ",
        "answer": "(the) desires",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ahwāa",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجِدُ",
        "answer": "(do) I find",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ajidu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَّهْتُ",
        "answer": "[I] have turned",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wajjahtu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهَهُ",
        "answer": "His Countenance",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wajhahu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهِيَ",
        "answer": "my face",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wajhiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدٌ",
        "answer": "One",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wāḥidun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةٍ",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatin",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُوحِيَ",
        "answer": "and has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "waūḥiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوحَىٰ",
        "answer": "is revealed",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yūḥā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوحِيَ",
        "answer": "It has been inspired",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ūḥiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوحَ",
        "answer": "it was inspired",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yūḥa",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوحِيَ",
        "answer": "has been inspired",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ūḥiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوحِي",
        "answer": "inspiring",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yūḥī",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيُوحُونَ",
        "answer": "inspire",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "layūḥūna",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوحِيَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ūḥiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُسْتَوْدَعٌ",
        "answer": "and a resting place",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wamus'tawdaʿun",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذَرِ",
        "answer": "And leave",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wadhari",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "leave them",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "dharhum",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَذَرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We will leave them",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wanadharuhum",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَذَرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "so leave them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fadharhum",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذَرُوا",
        "answer": "Forsake",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wadharū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَذَرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "So leave them",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fadharhum",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَقَةٍ",
        "answer": "any leaf",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "waraqatin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَاءَ",
        "answer": "behind",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "warāa",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they bear",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yazirūna",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزِرُ",
        "answer": "bears",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taziru",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْزَارَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their burdens",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "awzārahum",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وِزْرَ",
        "answer": "burden",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wiz'ra",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَازِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "any bearer of burden",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wāziratun",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمِيزَانَ",
        "answer": "and the weight",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-mīzāna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسِعَ",
        "answer": "Encompasses",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wasiʿa",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُسْعَهَا",
        "answer": "(to) its capacity",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wus'ʿahā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسِعَةٍ",
        "answer": "Vast",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wāsiʿatin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصِفُونَ",
        "answer": "they attribute",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaṣifūna",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصْفَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(for) their attribution",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "waṣfahum",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصِلُ",
        "answer": "reach",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaṣilu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصِلُ",
        "answer": "reaches",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaṣilu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَّاكُمُ",
        "answer": "enjoined you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "waṣṣākumu",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَّاكُمْ",
        "answer": "(He) has enjoined on you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waṣṣākum",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَّاكُمْ",
        "answer": "(He) has enjoined on you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "waṣṣākum",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَّاكُمْ",
        "answer": "(He) has enjoined on you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waṣṣākum",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوعَدُونَ",
        "answer": "you are promised",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tūʿadūna",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْفُوا",
        "answer": "And give full",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wa-awfū",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْفُوا",
        "answer": "fulfil",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "awfū",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَفَّاكُمْ",
        "answer": "takes your (soul)",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yatawaffākum",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَفَّتْهُ",
        "answer": "take him",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "tawaffathu",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقْرًا",
        "answer": "deafness",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "waqran",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُقِفُوا",
        "answer": "they are made to stand",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wuqifū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُقِفُوا",
        "answer": "they will be made to stand",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wuqifū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) God conscious",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(become) righteous",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوهُ",
        "answer": "and fear Him",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqūhu",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "become righteous",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "tattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "and fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have entrusted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wakkalnā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِوَكِيلٍ",
        "answer": "a manager",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "biwakīlin",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلٌ",
        "answer": "a Guardian",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wakīlun",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِوَكِيلٍ",
        "answer": "a manager",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "biwakīlin",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِالْوَالِدَيْنِ",
        "answer": "and with the parents",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wabil-wālidayni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَدٌ",
        "answer": "a son",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "waladun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلَادِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their children ",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "awlādihim",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلَادَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their children",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "awlādahum",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلَادَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your children",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "awlādakum",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُوَلِّي",
        "answer": "We make friends",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "nuwallī",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْلَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "their Protector ",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "mawlāhumu",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيًّا",
        "answer": "(as) a protector",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "waliyyan",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٌّ",
        "answer": "any protector",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "waliyyun",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٌّ",
        "answer": "any protector",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "waliyyun",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَائِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their friends",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "awliyāihim",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "(will be) their protecting friend",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "waliyyuhum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاؤُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their friends",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "awliyāuhum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوَهَبْنَا",
        "answer": "And We bestowed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wawahabnā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَابِسٍ",
        "answer": "dry",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yābisin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَتِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the orphans",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-yatīmi",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their hands",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "bi-aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْهِ",
        "answer": "its hands",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yadayhi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands (saying)",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُوقِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones who are certain",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-mūqinīna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their oaths",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "aymānihim",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْعِهِ",
        "answer": "and its ripening",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayanʿihi",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a Day",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yawmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِكُمْ",
        "answer": "(of) your day",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yawmikum",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "347",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "Today",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "351",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) day",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "6",
        "ayah": "158"
    }
]; 
export default words;